

TRAN MINH PHUON

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

I am a web developer with over 8 months of experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript. I have knowledge of popular frameworks like React.js, Next.js and experience with REST APIs and improving website performance. "Always orient yourself to develop every day, keep emotional heat in all work."

CONTACT



minhphuongk57.dev@gmail.com

Binh Chanh, Ho Chi Minh City

in linkedin.com/in/minhphuongk57

github.com/minhphuongk57

SKILL

NextJS Git

ReactJs Figma

Javascript Photoshop

Typescript Illustrastor

HTML, CSS (SCSS) MySQL

TailwindCSS, Bootstrap Teamwork

EDUCATION

Cao Thang Technical College
2019 - 2022
Information Technology
Software Engineering Major

CAREER GOALS

Become a Full-stack developer.

EXPERIENCE

FABA Technology - Intern (03/2022 - 06/2022)

Faba Web As a product introduction to the company

Role: Working position Frontend and Backend. Technologies: **ReactJS**, **CMS(Strapi)**, **Axios**,

Styled-components.

Responsibilities:

- Use styled-components to build interfaces.
- Use strapi to create a new API for Faba-Web.
- Complete fixing of existing bugs (Case Study).

Website: https://fabatechnology.com/cases

Freelance - FE | Design (07/2021 - 04/2022)

- Front-end Developer: Cut HTML from PSD, Figma. Adobe XD. Cut UI from Figma with ReactJS.

- Design: stickers, banners, logos.

FES Solution - Fresher(07/2022 - 02/2023)

This is an admin page for managing the gym Role: Front-end Developer.

Technologies: NextJS, Typesript, React-Bootstrap, styled-components, Axios, Strapi.

Responsibilities:

- Build UI from Figma.
- Complete fixing of existing bugs.

PROIECT

Web Portfolio - Personal Project(07/2021) ReactJS, WowJS, Styled-Components, Git. https://minhphuongk57.github.io/MinhPhuongK57-Portfolio/

Portfolio Management 3D - (02/2023)

ReactJS, Vite, ThreeJS, TailwindCSS, Framemotion,... https://minhphuong.netlify.app/

PTPStore E-commerce System - (07/2022) PHP(Laravel), Flutter, Socket, axios, lodash, laravel-mix, firebase, material-design.

https://gitlab.com/phamtantai0901/repo-ptpstore-v.2